<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://degatchi.com/articles</id>
    <title>DeGatchi's Articles</title>
    <updated>2024-11-01T05:39:02.371Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <icon>https://degatchi.com/favicon.ico</icon>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seesaw]]></title>
        <id>https://degatchi.com/articles/seesaw</id>
        <link href="https://degatchi.com/articles/seesaw"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[Who dares enter the darkness to find the light?]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deducing God Exists With Logic?]]></title>
        <id>https://degatchi.com/articles/deducing-god-exists-with-logic</id>
        <link href="https://degatchi.com/articles/deducing-god-exists-with-logic"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[Can Mathematics convert your religious beliefs? I think it's so. Through the power of reason and logic you can get to a new perspective.]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Retard's Mathematical Evolutionary Philosophy]]></title>
        <id>https://degatchi.com/articles/mathematical-evolutionary-philosophy</id>
        <link href="https://degatchi.com/articles/mathematical-evolutionary-philosophy"/>
        <updated>2024-09-09T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[What happens when you combine existential philosophy w/ the background of mathematical mutation-based evolutionary biology? A borderline crazy person or a genius? Who knows! Let's take a look into the mind of DeGatchi as we explore the world of artificial possibilities.]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Perfect Plan]]></title>
        <id>https://degatchi.com/articles/the-perfect-plan</id>
        <link href="https://degatchi.com/articles/the-perfect-plan"/>
        <updated>2024-09-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[Too often do we obsess over the perfect plan to chase our dreams, resulting in analysis paralysis. Instead of being stuck in this limbo, I've made the perfect plan for anyone to chase their dreams.]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dream A Little]]></title>
        <id>https://degatchi.com/articles/dream-a-little</id>
        <link href="https://degatchi.com/articles/dream-a-little"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[It's saddening to see 99% of people lose their spark as they reach adulthood. From curious driven children to mindless robots, oh what a world we live in, or should I say exist in for most. If money wasn't an issue what would you do? If you can't answer this then you have a big problem, anon-kun.]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learning Is Hard...]]></title>
        <id>https://degatchi.com/articles/learning-is-hard</id>
        <link href="https://degatchi.com/articles/learning-is-hard"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[When we look at people better than us in a certain something we often don't consider the amount of pain and suffering that person went through to get to that point. A level 3 crook wants to be world-class at something but doesn't go through the torturous regime it takes to get to level 99 and reap the rewards. It's okay, anon-kun. I'm here to eliminate the fog of war and show you the limelight!]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Quadratics (WIP)]]></title>
        <id>https://degatchi.com/articles/understanding-quadratics</id>
        <link href="https://degatchi.com/articles/understanding-quadratics"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[Not getting quadratics? Same! With today's mental gym sesh we're doing leg day, focusing on quadratics. I know, the dreaded quadratic. Fuck them. But we need to understand them to move onto the other cool shit in math. Lets see whether we can get it to click!]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlocking Algebra (WIP)]]></title>
        <id>https://degatchi.com/articles/unlocking-algebra</id>
        <link href="https://degatchi.com/articles/unlocking-algebra"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[Want to learn math but not sure how to start? Feel like you're bad at math? Or maybe, you know different parts of math but there are holes in your mental model. Follow DeGatchi along this ride to get an intuition of how math works algebraically, as he once was 'bad at math' and had completely fragmented mental math models.]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building A Brand]]></title>
        <id>https://degatchi.com/articles/build-a-brand</id>
        <link href="https://degatchi.com/articles/build-a-brand"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most powerful forms of leverage, that lasts a lifetime, is branding. Whether business or personal branding the concepts apply to both. Branding is the association between entity and things you want to relate to. Whether you're an entrepreneur or a person sitting at your desk at 2 am contemplating 'How do I make content', 'I want to express how I feel', 'I need to share my thoughts with the world in hopes someone, anyone, can find me, relate to me in this desolate sphere we call home' then you're in the right place!]]></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leaving For London]]></title>
        <id>https://degatchi.com/articles/leaving-for-london</id>
        <link href="https://degatchi.com/articles/leaving-for-london"/>
        <updated>2024-01-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[Enter the mind of DeGatchi as he moves continents, once again! Ever wondered what happens in a developer's life? Someone you relate to or look up to? In this article DeGatchi exaplains his rationale for leaving his home country to venture into a new one to start a new life -- all in the name of *blank*...]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>